{
    "data": [
      {"question": "How do I reset my password?", "answer": "You can reset your password by following..."},
      {"question": "What is the meaning of life?", "answer": "The meaning of life is subjective and varies..."},
        {"question": "introduce vcet", "answer": "Vivekananda College of Engineering & Technology (VCET), Puttur, one of the reputed engineering colleges in the coastal region of Karnataka, was established in the year 2001 by Vivekananda Vidyavardhaka Sangha Puttur (R) with the vision of providing quality technical education to the rural parts of coastal Karnataka."},
        {"question": " Vcet contact number", "answer": "9945575955"},
        {"question": " VCET CET code", "answer": "E121"},
        {"question": " VCET location", "answer": "Nehru Nagar, Puttur, Dakshina Kannada, Karnataka, 574203. INDIA"},
        {"question": " many course pg vcet", "answer": "8"},
        {"question": " many BE courses", "answer": "6"},
        {"question": " the HOD of Basic Science", "answer": "Prof.Ramanand Kamath"},
        {"question": "Number of seats available in computer science engineering", "answer": "120"},
        {"question": "Number of seats available in Data Science", "answer": "60"},
        {"question": "Number of seats available in Mechanical Engineering", "answer": "30"},
        {"question": "Number of seats available in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning", "answer": "60"},
        {"question": "Number of seats available in Civil Engineering", "answer": "30"},
        {"question": "Number of seats available in Electronics and communication Engineering", "answer": "60"},
        {"question": " Vivekananda Vidyavardhaka Sangha Puttur found", "answer": "Vivekananda Vidyavardhaka Sangha Puttur® (VVSP: Formerly known as Puttur Education Society) was founded on the 23rd of December 1915."},
        {"question": " VCET located", "answer": "Nehru Nagar, Puttur, Dakshina Kannada, Karnataka, 574203. INDIA"},
        {"question": " contact number of office", "answer": "Phone: +91-8251-235955\nFax: +91-8251–236444\nMobile: 9945575955/9945577955"},
        {"question": " contact number of admission cell", "answer": "Prof. Vandana Shankar\nContact: 9945575955\nDr. Chethan P.D\nContact: 9945577955"},
        {"question": " contact details of placement cell", "answer": "Prof. Vandana Shankar, Training & Placement Officer\nPhone:08251-234555\nCell: 9945575955\nE-mail:placement@vcetputtur.ac.in"},
        {"question": "  contact details of principal of vcet", "answer": "Dr. Mahesh Prasanna\nEmail : principal@vcetputtur.ac.in,\nPhone: +91 99450 16992"},
        {"question": "How to get into VCET", "answer": "You can get in either by Management seat or CET entrance exam"},
        {"question": "Management seats are currently available in VCET", "answer": "You can get to know about seats by contacting our admission cell. Contact No:9945575955"},
        {"question": " fees structure amount for Engineering", "answer": "You can get to know about fees by contacting our admission cell.Contact No:9945575955"},
        {"question": " CSE fees", "answer": "It might vary from 1.5 lakh-2 lakh. For confirmation, you can contact our admission cell. Contact No:9945575955"},
        {"question": " far college is from Neharu-Nagara", "answer": "250 meters"},
        {"question": " college Timings", "answer": "9:00 am to 5:00 pm"},
        {"question": "Is VCET autonomous or VTU", "answer": "VCET is under VTU"},
        {"question": " HOD of cse", "answer": "KrishnaMohana A J is the HOD of CSE"},
        {"question": " HOD of ec", "answer": "Shrikanth Rao is the HOD of Electronics and communication"},
        {"question": " HOD of E&C", "answer": "Shrikanth Rao is the HOD of Electronics and communication"},
        {"question": " HOD of aiml", "answer": "Govindraj P is the HOD of AIML"},
        {"question": " cutoff", "answer": "It varies for different branches. For more information contact our admission cell. Contact No:9945575955"},
        {"question": " cutoff to get admission in VCET", "answer": "It varies for different branches. For more information contact our admission cell. Contact No:9945575955"},
        {"question": "hostel facility available", "answer": "Yes VCET provides hostel for both Girls and Boys"},
        {"question": "Canteen available in VCET", "answer": "Yes, Canteen facility has been given for both staff and students"},
        {"question": "Canteen in VCET", "answer": "Yes, Canteen facility has been given for both staff and students"},
        {"question": " bus facility available", "answer": "Yes, College bus facility is given for students"},
        {"question": "Is transportation available in VCET", "answer": "College bus facility is given for students"},
        {"question": " PG courses are available in VCET", "answer": "There are two PG courses available in VCET, 1) MBA 2) MCA"},
        {"question": " UG courses available", "answer": "BE in CSE, AIML, CSE(CD), E&C, Civil, Mech"},
        {"question": " PG courses available", "answer": "MBA and MCA are the two PG courses available in VCET"},
        {"question": " courses available in VCET", "answer": "UG: BE in CSE, AIML, CSE(CD), E&C, Civil, Mech and PG: MBA and MCA"},
        {"question": " Mahesh prasanna", "answer": "Principal of VCET"},
        {"question": " Principal of VCET", "answer": " Mahesh prasanna"},
        {"question": "Uniform of VCET", "answer": "All the four-year Engineering students are given the same uniform. MBA and MCA students wear formals."},
  {"question": "Number of Blocks in VCET", "answer": "There are three blocks in VCET."},
  {"question": "Sudarshana block", "answer": "Sudharshana block is the main block of VCET."},
  {"question": " block CSE department is located", "answer": "CSE department is located in Sudharshana block."},
  {"question": " block E&C department is located", "answer": "E&C department is located in Sudharshana block."},
  {"question": " block AIML department is located", "answer": "AIML department is located in Krishna Chethana block."},
  {"question": " block CD department is located", "answer": "CD department is located in Krishna Chethana block."},
  {"question": " block CIVIL department is located", "answer": "CIVIL department is located in Madhu Chethana block."},
  {"question": " block Mechanical department is located", "answer": "Mechanical department is located in Krishna Chethana block."},
  {"question": " ieee in VCET", "answer": "IEEE student branch is present in VCET."},
  {"question": " EEE branch there in VCET", "answer": "No, there is no EEE branch, only CSE, AIML, CSE(CD), E&C, Civil, Mech."},
  {"question": " library", "answer": "Yes, VCET has a vast library"},
  {"question": "  wifi", "answer": "Yes"},
  {"question": "computer labs laboratory facility", "answer": "Vcet has large number of computer labs "},
  {"question": " President of vcet", "answer": "Sri K Vishwas Shenoy"},
{"question": " Correspondent vcet", "answer": "Sri T S Subrahmanya Bhat"},
{"question": " Treasurer of vcet", "answer": "Sri Muralidhara Bhat B"},
{"question": " Member of the Governing Council with a background in Medicine?", "answer": "Dr. Suresh Putturaya"},
{"question": "Member of the Governing Council with a background in Civil Engineering?", "answer": "Sri Sathyanarayana B"},
{"question": "Secretary of vcet", "answer": "Dr. Mahesh Prasanna K"},
{"question": " Assistant Professor and Department Coordinator representing the staff?", "answer": "Ms. Sowmya Anil"},
{"question": " Director of VVS", "answer": "Sri. Balarama Acharya"},
{"question": " President of VVS", "answer": "Dr. Kalladka Prabhakar Bhat"},
{"question": " Secretary of VVS", "answer": "Dr. K. M. Krishna Bhat"},
{"question": " average graduation rate at VCET?", "answer": "The average graduation rate at VCET is 98%."},
{"question": " services does VCET offer for student counseling and guidance?", "answer": "Experienced faculty provide student counseling and guidance at VCET."},
{"question": " IT infrastructure at vcet described?", "answer": "VCET has the best IT infrastructure for academic, administrative, and support systems."},
{"question": " type of internet connectivity does vcet provide for 24 hours?", "answer": "VCET offers leased line internet connectivity for 24 hours with a speed of 230Mbps."},
{"question": "List the faculty members of the Computer Science & Engineering Department at VCET.","answer": "1. Mr. Krishna Mohana A J - HOD\n2. Dr. Lokesh M R - Professor\n3. Dr. Uma Pare - Associate Professor\n4. Dr. Jeevitha B K - Associate Professor\n5. Ms. Roopa G K - Assistant Professor\n6. Ms. Bharathi K - Assistant Professor\n7. Ms. Radhika Shetty D S - Assistant Professor\n8. Mrs. Savitha M - Assistant Professor\n9. Mr. Pradeep Kumar K G - Assistant Professor\n10. Mr. Mohan A R - Assistant Professor\n11. Ms. Swapnalaxmi K - Assistant Professor\n12. Mr. Pramod Kumar P M - Assistant Professor\n13. Ms. Thapaswini P S - Assistant Professor\n14. Ms. Deepthi M B - Assistant Professor\n15. Ms. Jayashree M - Assistant Professor\n16. Manohar Jha - Assistant Professor\n17. Mr. Shrinidhi A - Assistant Professor\n18. Ms. Manasa P - Assistant Professor\n\nNon-Teaching Faculty:\n19. Mr. Sharath K S - System Administrator\n20. Mrs. Navyashree P - Lab Instructor\n21. Mr. Jagadeesha K H - Lab Instructor\n22. Mr. Prashantha M S - Lab Instructor\n23. Mrs. Bhavyashree - Lab Instructor\n24. Mr. Rakesh K - Lab Instructor\n25. Mr. Ganesh - Attender"},
{"question": "List the teaching faculty members of the Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning Department at VCET.", "answer": "1. Dr. Govindaraj P - Associate Professor & Head\n2. Mrs. Akshaya D. Shetty - Assistant Professor\n3. Ms. Monica.K.P - Assistant Professor\n4. Mr. Abhishek Kumar K - Assistant Professor\n5. Mr. Ajay Shastry C G - Assistant Professor\n6. Mrs. Vaishnavi K V - Assistant Professor\n7. Mr.Venkatesh Y C - Assistant Professor\n8. Mr. Naveena C - Assistant Professor\n9. Ms. Shruthi P. R - Assistant Professor\n\nNon-Teaching Faculty:\n10. Ms. Harshitha - Lab Instructor"},
{"question": " companies Computer Science and Engineering (CSE) branch.", "answer": "1. INFOSYS\n2. TCS\n3. THOUGHT FOCUS\n4. GLOBAL DELIGHT\n5. JUEGO STUDIO\n6. OPEN FIVE\n7. SPEC BEE\n8. IBM\n9. AAVALI SOLUTIONS\n10. MAVENTIC INNOVATIVE SOLUTIONS PVT LTD.\n11. SIGN DESK\n12. TENXER TECHNOLOGIES\n13. SLK SOFTWARE\n14. GLOBAL AUTOMATION\n15. RED HAT\n16. BES CONSULTANCY\n17. EXCELACOM TECHNOLOGY PVT LTD\n18. ROBOSOFT TECHNOLOGIES\n19. PACE WISDOM SOLUTIONS\n20. FLAIR LABS\n21. LOCKTELL SOLUTIONS\n22. LUMEN TECHNOLOGIES\n23. STRAECON\n24. SMARTCACHE\n25. DIFACTO ROBOTICS AND AUTOMATIVE PVT LTD\n26. ACCORD SOFTWARE\n27. PRINTALYTICS\n28. ALEMBIC PHARMACEUTICALS LTD\n29. DIYA STSYEMS (GLOWTUCH )\n30. NAXEVA TECHNOLOGIES\n31. SEVENTH SENSE\n32. OSHIMA SYSTEMS PRIVATE LTD\n33. TECHNOLOGIES GLOBAL\n34. WUERTH ELEKTRONIK INDIA PVT LTD MYSORE\n35. VIDHAATRI TECHNOLOGY BANGALORE\n36. ETHNUS\n37. SIGNOFF SEMICONDUCTORS\n38. ACMEGRADE\n39. TAYANA SOFTWARE\n40. BREVERA TECHNOLOGY PVT LTD\n41. TECH MAHINDRA\n42. CAPSTONE ORGANISATION\n43. ETHNUS\n44. DIYA STSYEMS (GLOWTUCH )\n45. KGI'S COIMATORE\n46. COGENT E SERVICES PVT LTD\n47. MANIPAL TECHNOLOGIES\n48. EPIANCE\n49. S & S SOLUTIONS\n50. INDO MIM\n51. SILICA DESIGN"},
{"question": "companies  Electronics and Communication Engineering (ECE) branch.", "answer": "1. SAP LABS\n2. CADENCE\n3. OPEN FIVE\n4. TESSOLVE\n5. SPEC BEE\n6. IBM\n7. AAVALI SOLUTIONS\n8. MAVENTIC INNOVATIVE SOLUTIONS PVT LTD.\n9. SIGN DESK\n10. TENXER TECHNOLOGIES\n11. SLK SOFTWARE\n12. GLOBAL AUTOMATION\n13. RAVICAB CABLES\n14. RED HAT\n15. WUERTH ELEKTRONIK INDIA PVT LTD MYSORE\n16. VIDHAATRI TECHNOLOGY BANGALORE\n17. ETHNUS\n18. CADD CENTRE\n19. ALOHA TECHNOLOGY\n20. SIGNOFF SEMICONDUCTORS\n21. ACMEGRADE\n22. KOSSA AUTO TECH PVT LTD\n23. AKTIS ENGINEERS\n24. TAYANA SOFTWARE\n25. BREVERA TECHNOLOGY PVT LTD\n26. TECH MAHINDRA\n27. INFINX SERVICES PVT LTD\n28. CAPSTONE ORGANISATION\n29. ETHNUS\n30. DIYA STSYEMS (GLOWTUCH )\n31. KGI'S COIMATORE\n32. COGENT E SERVICES PVT LTD\n33. MANIPAL TECHNOLOGIES\n34. EPIANCE\n35. SHAH EXPORTS"},
{"question": "companies Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning (AIML) branch.", "answer": "1. SAP LABS\n2. CADENCE\n3. THOUGHT FOCUS\n4. GLOBAL DELIGHT\n5. OPEN FIVE\n6. JUEGO STUDIO\n7. TESSOLVE\n8. SPEC BEE\n9. IBM\n10. AAVALI SOLUTIONS\n11. HP\n12. MAVENTIC INNOVATIVE SOLUTIONS PVT LTD.\n13. SIGN DESK\n14. TENXER TECHNOLOGIES\n15. SLK SOFTWARE\n16. GLOBAL AUTOMATION\n17. RED HAT\n18. EXCELACOM TECHNOLOGY PVT LTD\n19. ROBOSOFT TECHNOLOGIES\n20. PACE WISDOM SOLUTIONS\n21. FLAIR LABS\n22. LOCKTELL SOLUTIONS\n23. LUMEN TECHNOLOGIES\n24. STRAECON\n25. SMARTCACHE\n26. DIFACTO ROBOTICS AND AUTOMATIVE PVT LTD\n27. ACCORD SOFTWARE\n28. AUTO LIVE\n29. PRINTALYTICS\n30. DIYA STSYEMS (GLOWTUCH )\n31. NAXEVA TECHNOLOGIES\n32. SEVENTH SENSE\n33. OSHIMA SYSTEMS PRIVATE LTD\n34. TECHNOLOGIES GLOBAL\n35. ETHNUS\n36. SIGNOFF SEMICONDUCTORS\n37. ACMEGRADE\n38. KOSSA AUTO TECH PVT LTD\n39. AKTIS ENGINEERS\n40. TAYANA SOFTWARE\n41. BREVERA TECHNOLOGY PVT LTD\n42. TECH MAHINDRA\n43. INFINX SERVICES PVT LTD\n44. CAPSTONE ORGANISATION\n45. ETHNUS\n46. DIYA STSYEMS (GLOWTUCH )\n47. KGI'S COIMATORE\n48. COGENT E SERVICES PVT LTD\n49. MANIPAL TECHNOLOGIES\n50. EPIANCE\n51. S & S SOLUTIONS"}





      
      
    ]
  }